Hey, Youngjae
Hey
Why didn't you come to the reunion yesterday?
Ah, I had some work to do.
The guys waited so much for you.
Hey, everyone's busy, but they made time to come.
Jisoo was making a fuss about wanting to see you.
Ah, really?
Yeah, make sure you come next time.
Okay, I got it.
Ah, reunions...
You need something to show off to go there.
What?
You're Choi Jaemin, right?
Class 5 of Yangseo High School, 2nd grade.
Yeah, that's right.
Kim Nam-i?
Yes.
Ah, at the reunion yesterday
We were really looking for you.
You didn't show up?
Ah, I had some work...
Ah, you were busy.
Did I interrupt you?
No, no, not at all.
I've just finished up.
No, remember when we skipped class together?
And we got caught by the homeroom teacher right away.
You got caught and I ran away.
The next day,
You never mentioned my name to the end.
Remember that?
Ah, did that happen?
Yes, it did.
I felt so sorry inside.
Watching you walk like a duck alone,
around the sports field.
I really thought that was true loyalty!
Ah, I remember now.
Right?
It was fun back then though.
Sorry but,
it's our closing time.
Oh sorry, I'll get up now.
Wow, it's already this late.
Where do you live?
I live in Ilsan.
Ilsan?
Then you have to take a bus.
Is there still a bus at this time?
I need to catch the last bus.
Let’s hurry.
We missed it.
What should we do?
Is it near your house?
My house?
Yes.
That’s fortunate.
Should we have a drink?
A drink?
Aren't you working tomorrow?
Me?
I'm not working.
Ah
Oh, you're the one working.
No, not really.
I'm not working either.
Not yet.
I'll buy the drinks.
Let's go.
Ah, why is it so cold?
Is the heater off?
How can it be colder inside?
Ah, right.
The gas was cut off.
It's been overdue for two months.
What should we do?
It's so cold.
What does it matter?
I have this here.
Ta-da!
Oh!
It's really not cold.
It's actually hot.
Right?
We can get through this winter with this.
Hey,
It's because you're awake.
If you sleep, you'll turn over.
I liked that about you.
What?
That you don't swear.
Swear?
Among the kids we hung out with,
was there anyone who didn't swear?
Every time they opened their mouth,
idiot,
punk,
nonsense.
If I said something silly,
I'd hear ten curses.
But you, you never cursed and
always responded so seriously.
Really?
That's why I liked it.
About you.
What you were doing in college,
I was curious about that.
Me?
Yeah, you.
You weren't curious about me, were you?
Well...
I did think of you occasionally.
Ah.. those were good times.
No worries about getting a job,
or about paying the gas bill.
It wasn’t that I missed you,
I missed those times.
That's it.
Hey,
I've been busy just trying to make a living.
Not tutoring, but working part-time jobs.
You're still popular, aren’t you?
Got a girlfriend?
Me?
Was I popular?
You were popular even back in school.
That...
Who was that pale-faced girl who followed you around?
That Jeong Hayoon.
Jeong Hayoon?
Yeah.
Hey, she was chasing you around,
crying and making a scene.
Why do you remember that stuff?
I didn’t even notice her that much back then.
At that time,
I was envious.
Just that.
If someone cried for me,
I wonder how painful that would feel, and yet,
on the other hand,
I think it’d be nice to experience that once.
Something like that.
Ah,
You used to love writing, didn't you?
That...
Was it at graduation?
You wrote the longest messages on the rolling paper,
I think you wrote the most.
I...
I cried reading that.
I said it back then too,
that you could make a living off your writing.
I was serious about that.
Right?
Hey,
It’s cold...
Jaemin,
Huh?