Hello?
What are you doing?
Just..
Why?
No.. do you remember Kim Nami?
Huh?
Uh.. I remember..
But why?
Ah.. you didn't get contacted, I see.
No, at the reunion, you were collecting everyone's numbers like that,
Asking for a magazine interview.
They said you caused such a scene.
Ah, but that magazine was an adult magazine.
Adult magazine.
Adult magazine?
Yes, something about writing a sex column?
So they told me not to associate with you anymore.
So you be careful too.
Ah..
Uh..
Hey, no matter how hard it is to find a job,
Is it okay to sell out your friends like that?
Wow, what a trashy guy.
But I guess he's also struggling to make a living.
If you're not exceptionally talented,
It's hard to make a living by writing.
That's why he does what he has to do to make a living.
Ugh! Don't worry, I'm not involved.
Yes.
Why?
Huh?
Ah..
About yesterday,
It was a mistake?
You made a mistake because you were drunk?
Do you want to believe that?
Huh?
You think
You think I hugged you just because I was really cold?
It wasn't because I was cold.
I said I was cold because I wanted to hug you.
Mistake.
No.
I'm just doing what my heart tells me to do.
Ah..
Your...
How does your heart feel?
I don't know.
Heart..
Do as your heart desires.
That's what I'm doing.
But..
Aren't you hungry?
Just a moment..
You..
Is this your usual way?
I'm not sure?
You're my first.
This is the first time I've felt this way towards a man.
So, just like you,
I'm a bit complicated too.
Ah
I feel like you're not saying anything,
and I look like a beginner,
and I'm afraid you'll dislike me even more.
Sorry.
No, it's not that.
How about you?
Have you ever felt this way?
You're my first too.
So,
I'm a bit scared.
Scared?
Of what?
Of liking you too much.
Even if I like you,
I'll like you more.
So,
don't worry.
- The unforgettable taste of first-time sex with a man -
Ah, what time is it now?
3 o'clock.
Ah, I only slept for 30 minutes.
What about you?
Hmm?
What are you?
Jaemin,
I'll explain everything.
It's not what
you think it is.
Let's go with the flow.
Did you mean to do whatever you want?
Well...
Did you read it?
No.
Just the title seemed interesting.
Do you exploit people's feelings like this?
What?
I heard from Yongjae.
Even at the reunion, you were insisting on a sex column interview.
You really caused a scene.
You're really something.
How can you show your face?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Yeah,
I thought you might misunderstand,
you should have read the whole thing.
Without reading it thoroughly,
it's disgusting.
What did you say?
I said your article is disgusting.
An article written exploiting someone's genuine feelings,
is it even worth reading?
Sigh...
Please pack your things and leave.
Were you,
sincere every moment?
Pretending to defend me,
complaining about how hard it is to make a living by writing,
was all that sincere too?
Just because you seem like a better person than me,
does that make you feel better?
What?
Don't make me laugh!
As if you're the only one who's sincere.
- Nami -