The first night with a man
The confusion bloomed within the fluttering feelings
When the breath of that child touched me
I returned to being an eighteen-year-old boy
Would that child feel the same?
The more I got to know that child
The confusion disappeared
And only fluttering, warm feelings remained by my side
How about it?
Is it weird?
No
Hmm..
I like it
You like it?
My writing?
Yes, it’s very honest
And warm
I was again...
Worried that you might think it strange
Though I couldn’t express everything in the writing
As written in the text, at first it was curiosity
Now, it's genuine
This is my answer
Huh?
Sorry for the misunderstanding
Oh, wait a second, I need to make a call.
Why isn't it going well?
Uh..
I'm not sure if what I'm writing is a personal statement
or a fictional story.
Take a look at it.
Uh..
This part feels awkward, so it might be better to remove it.
This part..
It would be better if it were smoothed out, right?
Just a moment.
How about now?
Oh, it really feels smoother now.
Mr. Choi Jaemin,
What are you going to do with me? You should use this opportunity.
In my opinion, a personal statement
shouldn't be written
with the intent of just trying to impress others.
Hmm.. then what?
It should naturally show that
you are proud of yourself through the writing.
Like..
Does it convey sincerity?
A forced, fabricated piece of writing
is something the reader can also feel.
Awkward and exaggerated
Hmm..
You must have at least one part you're confident in
It would be good to focus on appealing that
Yes
Ah.. why
Because it's cute
Oppa
Hey, what are you doing here?
Sangmyeong Oppa said
Oppa usually works here
Came looking for Oppa
He wouldn’t even eat when I asked
Who? A friend?
Yeah, my classmate Jaemin
Oh, hello
All of Oppa's friends are handsome
Can I sit?
Sure
Ah
Oppa was really popular in college, you know?
All my friends lined up asking to be introduced
Hey!
It wasn't that much, you know?
What lineup?
So you’re not busy, then
Why won’t you eat with me?
You’re busy
I’m not busy, you know?
Look at this
Always making excuses to avoid me
Do you have a lover
Hidden away somewhere?
Ah.. I guess?
Hey, whether I have a lover or not
What’s it to you?
What’s it to you
Or not
But are you doing well at work?
Yes, of course
Do you know how much my seniors adore me?
Hey, are you working at JK Company? Are you preparing for that?
Ah..
Oh, oppa, are you also preparing to apply to our company?
If so, I'll give you some job application tips.
Can I have your number?
What kind of trick is this?
Is this a new type of flirting or what?
Ah!
Crazy..
Oh no, what do I do? I'm late for my part-time job now.
I need to go.
Hey, you work a part-time job too?
Yeah, just for today.
Ah, that's not what's important right now.
Oppa, can you drop me off just up ahead?
Hey, are you a child?
Ah, why? It's been a while since we last met.
Just to the taxi stand.
Huh?
I’ll drop you off and come back.
Ah, you really are tiring.
Let's go.
See you next time.
Yes.
honey.