Wow, the weather is really nice.
Shall we go out?
To the amusement park.
Or
The beach?
Jaemin.
Why.. again?
Because of Sol?
He's always a bit out of it.
Don't mind him.
What's wrong?
You
Have you been hiding a lover?
A lover?
What lover?
On your phone...
Who is this?
Ah..
Ah!
Honey
Oh, what am I saying again.
Do you find this amusing?
Ah, sorry.
Sorry.
Hold on.
Honey
What are you doing?
Son!
Yes, it's me.
Why are you calling first all of a sudden?
Did you eat?
Did mom eat?
Mom ate just a bit ago.
Uh-huh.
I'll be coming home later.
I love you.
You...
You still don't know me.
Were you worried?
Yes.
What if we do this outside?
Don't do that, it's ticklish.
How about here?
You said you had to leave, right?
Ah, right.
I'll be late.
Why does time go by so fast?
Hmm.. I'll go take a shower and come back.
Hello?
Jaemin oppa?
Hmm..
It's Sori.
Ah, it's Sori.
But what's up?
Oppa, do you have some time tomorrow?
Huh?
Me?
Yes, I have something to tell you.
Ah, don't tell anyone else, okay?
Uh..
Uh, yeah, okay.
See you tomorrow.
I ordered just any coffee.
Uh, thanks.
I..
Likes Nami oppa.
You know?
Uh..
I didn't know?
Has it been about 3 years?
I first fell for him at the OT.
I've been following him ever since.
Confessing...
Did you?
Of course.
But oppa sees me only as a younger sibling.
Ah..
That must have been upsetting.
Nami oppa was popular, but...
He never really had a serious girlfriend, you know?
Just dated for fun and broke up.
So I was relieved...
But oppa seems different.
What does that mean...
What do you like about Nami oppa?
His good looks?
His height?
Or...
The way he spends money?
I don't understand what you're saying...
I knew it right from the start.
Ah..
So, Nam is oppa's new lover.
This time it's a man?
Don't meet with oppa, Nam.
What?
Because I like oppa, Nam.
Don't meet him.
Ah..
I'm so dumbfounded I'm speechless.
Is it because of Sol?
Whether Nam dates someone or not,
that's Nam's freedom.
Same for me.
I don't think you have the right to order people around.
I'll go first.
Oppa, are you currently preparing for JK Enterprise?
And Miseong Enterprise would be the second choice?
Most of my friends and I are too.
We are all in that field.
If it gets out that a man is dating another man,
even if it's just a rumor,
I wonder if they can even work properly at the company?
What about oppa, Nam?
Whether he dates men or women,
he lives well without any worries about finding a job,
since his family is wealthy.
But how about you, oppa?
Employment,
is it okay if you don't get one?
It doesn't make sense, does it?
Jaemin
What's bothering you?
Is something wrong?
It's just that we're in different situations!
Let's just stop this.
What?
You might not like being ordinary, but
I want to live an ordinary life at least.
Are you serious?
Words that can't be taken back...
Don't say them.
I'm serious.
Take care.
I'll ask you one last thing.
If you let go of this hand now,
Is it really the end for us?
Heart...
Do as it wishes.
Even if you like me,
I will like you more.